var myQuestions = [

    // The below array containing object literal, which is a comma-seperated list of name-value pairs

    // First question. 
    {
        question: "What symbol comes after a function?",
        choices: [
            ";",
            "()",
            "{}",
            "[]",
        ],

        correctAnswer: 1
    },

    // Second question 
    {
        question: "Which function converts an argument to a string and returns a floating point number?",
        choices: [
            "parseFloat()",
            "toFixed()",
            "valueOf()",
            "toString()",],

        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    // Third question 
    {
        question: "Which method combines the text of two strings and turns them into one string?",
        choices: ["concat()",
            "charAt()",
            "length()",
            "match()",
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },




    // Fourth question 
    {
        question: "Which symbol means equal value and equal type?",
        choices: [
            "=",

            "==",

            "===",

            "!=",
        ],

        correctAnswer: "2"

    },

    // Fifth question
    {
        question: "Which method formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?",
        choices: [
            "toPrecision",
            "valueOf",
            "toExponential",
            "toFixed",
        ],

        correctAnswer: "3"
    },

    // Sixth question
    {
        question: "Which symbol means 'or'?",
        choices: [
            "&",

            "|",

            "||",

            "~",
        ],

        correctAnswer: "2"
    },

    // Seventh question
    {
        question: "Which function determines whether a value is an illegal number?",
        choices: [
            "parseInt",
            "isNan",
            "decodeURI",
            "isFinite",
        ],

        correctAnswer: "1"
    },

    // Eigth question
    {
        question: "All properties have a name and a what?",
        choices: [
            "attribute",

            "value",

            "element",
            "function",
        ],

        correctAnswer: "1"
    },

    // Ninth question
    {
        question: "Where is the the optimal location to place the linking <script> tag in an HTML document?",
        choices: [
            "right after </body>",
            "right before </body>",
            "right before </head>",
            "right after </head>",
        ],

        correctAnswer: "1"
    },

    // Tenth question
    {
        question: "Which one is not a JavaScript datatype?",
        choices: [
            "Symbols",

            "Numbers",

            "Booleans",

            "strings",
        ],

        correctAnswer: "0"
    }
];